<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Shoptastic</string>
    <string name="women1">Fashion Web Women\'s Georgette Embroidered Semi-Stitched Anarkali Gown Style; Anarkali Dress; Long Gown; Care Instructions: Hand Wash Only</string>
    <string name="women2">Slim Fit Jeans; Material: 73% Cotton, 25% Poly, 2% Spandex; High Rise; Stretchable; Zip fly with button closure; Machine wash warm, wash dark colors separately, do not bleach, tumble dry low, warm iron</string>
    <string name="men1">Inkast Casual Shirt; Care Instructions: Machine Wash; Fit Type: Slim Fit Soft and Breathable; 100% Cotton Fabric; Garment dyed solid color shirt</string>
    <string name="mob1">" Roll over image to zoom in Samsung Galaxy M52 5G (ICY Blue, 6GB RAM, 128GB Storage) Latest Snapdragon 778G 5G | sAMOLED 120Hz Display"</string>
    <string name="mob2">Nature Green, 2GB RAM, 32GB Storage) | 2GHz Octa-core Helio G25 Processor | 5000 mAh Battery</string>
    <string name="book1">This story, dazzling in its powerful simplicity and inspiring wisdom, is about an Andalusian shepherd boy named Santiago who travels from his homeland in Spain to the Egyptian desert in search of a treasure buried in the Pyramids. Along the way he meets a Gypsy woman, a man who calls himself</string>
    <string name="book2">‘Eleven minutes’ is the masterpiece of Brazilian bestselling author Paulo Coelho. This novel is based on a fictional account of a woman named Maria who lives in Rio, but moves to Geneva.</string>
    <string name="women3">ESPRESSO Women\'s 100% Viscose Waterfall Shrugs with Button Foldable Sleeve; Care Instructions: Machine Wash; Fit Type: Regular</string>
    <string name="women4">VERO MODA Women\'s Single Breasted Blazer Slim; Care Instructions: Dry Clean Only; Color Name: Port Royale</string>
    <string name="women5">Care Instructions: Machine Wash; Fit Type: Regular; 60% Cotton and 40% polyester; Hooded SweatshirtSolid</string>
    <string name="women6">Uptownie Lite Women\'s Midi Skirt; Occasion : Suitable for Casual, Party, Regular Wear, Occasions, Christmas, Night out, New Years and Gifting.; Care Instructions: Machine Wash</string>
    <string name="women7">Care Instructions: Machine Wash; Fit Type: Regular Fit; Made from Polyester Blend Fabric</string>
    <string name="book3">Set in the lonely and bleak Yorkshire moors, this classic tale of thwarted passion begins when the new tenant of Thrushcross Grange, a Mr Lockwood, is forced to seek shelter for a night at Wuthering Heights</string>
</resources>